https://www.cheshiregunroom.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Menu
Package DealsAccessory Packs & Cleaning KitsAir Gun Accessory PacksShotgun Accessory PacksShotgun Cleaning KitsCrossbow KitsGun KitsAir Gun KitsGun RoomShotgunsOver and UndersSide by SidesSingle BarrelsPump ActionsMagazine FedSemi-Auto ShotgunsPractical ShotgunsModerated ShotgunsJunior ShotgunsLever Action ShotgunsHammer GunsPre-Owned ShotgunsRiflesRimfireCentre FireUnderleverSound ModeratorsMini-RiflePre-Owned RiflesAir RiflesSpring Air RiflesCO2 Air RiflesPre-Charged Air RiflesFAC / Hi-Power Air RiflesGas Ram Air RiflesJunior Air RiflesPre-Owned Air RiflesAir PistolsSpring Air PistolsCO2 Air PistolsPre-Charged Air PistolsPneumatic Air PistolsPre-Owned Air PistolsPistolsNew PistolsUsed PistolsPractical PistolsMiscellaneousBlank Firing GunsDe-activated GunsObsolete & Antique GunsCrossbowsCombination Guns0% Finance Available from £250 to £15,000
Popular Brands
OpticsScopes25mm (1") Tube30mm TubeIlluminatedSpottingSpotting ScopesBinocularsRange FindersMonocularsNight OpticsNV Rifle ScopesNV BinocularsMonocularsNight Vision AccessoriesThermal RiflescopesRed Dots & LasersRed DotsLasersAccessoriesMountsLens CoversLens CleaningHarnessesCasesSun ShadesBatteriesCamerasOthers0% Finance Available from £250 to £15,000
Popular Brands
SecuritySecurity EquipmentGun CabinetsPistols / Ammo CabinetsFixing KitsTrigger LocksLockable Carry CasesClothing & FootwearMensTrousersJacketsVestsFleecesPulloversT-ShirtsShirtsLadiesJacketsVestsShirtsChildrenFootwearAccessoriesHatsGlovesCufflinksTiesFootwearWellingtonsWalking BootsShoesAccessoriesPopular Clothing Brands
ReloadingEquipmentDiesToolsPressesPowder MeasuresMediaLubricationScalesKitsTumblersAccessoriesComponentsBrass / CasesBullet HeadsPowderPrimersPopular Reloading Brands
Gun CareEquipmentCleaning KitsPull ThroughsRodsBore GuidesGun Rests / VicesBrushes Mops & JagsSnap CapsTools / StorageCleaning AgentsStock TreatmentMetal TreatmentOil / LubricantsCleaners / SolventsCleaning PatchesCleaning ClothsPopular Gun Care Brands
AccessoriesGeneralGame & Field BagsRange Boxes / BagsHearing ProtectionEye ProtectionGun Sling & StrapsSwivels & AttachmentsGun Slips & CasesPin BadgesLicense HoldersCups & FlasksSlingshots & AmmoTools & KnivesSeat SticksHand WarmersStocksBooks & DVDsMiscellaneousRifleBipodsMagazinesScope MountsBullet StorageTargetsLens CoversSound ModeratorsSnap CapsRecoil PadsFox CallsShooting SticksShotgunClay TrapsRecoil PadsComb RaisersChokesBeads & End SightsCartridge Bags / StorageCoachingSnap CapsMiscellaneousChoke Keys & CasesSound ModeratorsMagazinesUsed CasesAir GunPellets and BBsChronographsBottles and GaugesSound ModeratorsCO2Stirrups PumpsTargetsMagazines and TraysFill Probes and Adaptors Recoil PadsBipods and RestsSpare PartsLens CoversField SportsDecoysGame CallsFerreting EquipmentTraps and SnaresLamping & BatteriesBatteries & ChargersAdapters & AttachmentsFiltersFlash LightsDog TrainingDummiesWhistlesLaunchers and BlanksPopular Brands
Christmas ShopChristmas Air Gun PackagesStocking FillersGifts Under £50Luxury GiftsChristmas Essentials
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Cheshire Gun Room Limited uses and protects any information that you give Cheshire Gun Room Limited when you use this website. Cheshire Gun Room Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Cheshire Gun Room Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@cheshiregunroom.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Cheshire Gun Room
29 Buxton Road,
Stockport
SK4 2JA
United Kingdom.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
ABOUT US
Welcome to Cheshire Gun Room, a leading shooting sports retailer located in Stockport and Bolton, North West of England.
Our areas of expertise and products cover Gunsmithing, Shotguns, Rifles, Air Guns and Optics.
Read more about us
USEFUL LINKS
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
Delivery and Returns
Security & Payments
Information Centre
CONTACT US
STOCKPORT 0161 480 8222Opening Times: Mon-Fri: 10am - 5:30pm
Sat: 9am - 5:30pm
BOLTON 01204 496 008Opening Times: Mon-Sat: 9:30am - 5:30pm
info@cheshiregunroom.com
stockport@cheshiregunroom.com
bolton@cheshiregunroom.com
exports@cheshiregunroom.com
Subscribe to our Newsletter
© 2020 Cheshire Gun Room Limited. All Rights Reserved.
Please select your shipping location to start shopping
Changing your shipping location may affect your shopping cart.
Country
AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d’IvoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacau SAR ChinaMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar (Burma)NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé and PríncipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayU.S. Minor Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
State/Province
Please select region, state or province
Cancel
Submit
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
Find out more here.
x
